Last Update: March 31, 2022

### Introduction

HomeProjectPros.org values your privacy and the security of your personal information. HomeProjectPros.org is committed to ensuring the information you provide is utilized responsibly and within the terms of our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to the information we collect on our website and surveys.

HomeProjectPros.org collects consumer opinions and related information for the following purposes:

* Understand the habits of our consumers in order to provide them with appropriate information and offers
* Send consumers information about HomeProjectPros.org
* Assist affiliate companies in marketing products and presenting new ones
* Provide you with information about the products and services we offer
* Provide you with a more personalised service
* Conduct market research
* Pass on to selected companies to provide you with offers and promotions
* Help other companies profile and extend their databases
* Facilitate communication between yourself and others

The following provides details on the type of information HomeProjectPros.org collects, how it is used and shared, as well as how to make changes to your membership.

### Type Of Information Collected

Contact Information: Basic contact information such as name, postal and email address may be collected so that you may participate in HomeProjectPros.org programs and offers. Postal address is required to send you samples, coupons and other offers via mail. Offers are also sent via email.

Survey Information: Information you share with HomeProjectPros.org through answering survey questions include demographic, financial, interests, goals and other information. The information you provide is utilized by HomeProjectPros.org and its partners to provide you with the appropriate offers based on your preferences.

Email Information: Upon sending emails, HomeProjectPros.org may collect data about whether the email was opened and the contents in the email that were clicked on. Web beacons may be placed within the email messages which enable us to collect this data and better target future communications based on your interests.

Social Media Features: HomeProjectPros.org may include the ability to share information about your activities via social media platforms. A cookie may be set to enable the feature to properly function. In the event you choose to log in to our website using social media sign-in services, these services will authenticate your identity and provide you with the option to share certain information with us to pre-populate the sign up form to participate in our surveys. Information collected via social media sign-in will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. All other social media features are governed by that social media company’s privacy policy.

Third Party Information: In order to provide you with more relevant information and offers, HomeProjectPros.org and its partner companies may utilize additional information provided by other companies.

Online Activity: Certain information about your online activity may also be collected by HomeProjectPros.org. Further information regarding this can be found under Cookies and Online Activities.

Other information may be collected by HomeProjectPros.org with your consent, or as permitted or required by law.

### How Info is Used and Shared

By providing us with your contact information and answering survey questions, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of said information for marketing and commercial purposes.

Product offers: Contact information and survey responses may be used by our partner companies to provide our members with free product samples, coupons, product information and other offers. This may be presented via email, postal mail, online advertising or telephone. If you wish to stop receiving these offers you can cancel your membership as stated below under Choices and Managing Your Membership.

Email Offers: HomeProjectPros.org may send you product offers via email based on your responses provided in our survey. These emails are sent by HomeProjectPros.org and not our partner companies. You may unsubscribe at any point by clicking the Unsubscribe link in the email received or by following the instructions stated below under Choices and Managing Your Membership.

Partner companies: When supplying your contact information and survey responses, you consent to HomeProjectPros.org sharing your information with our partner companies in order for them to send you samples, information and offers most appropriate for you. All of our partnerships have contractual agreements to ensure that the information they receive is handled securely. Email messages may include links to sites not affiliated with HomeProjectPros.org and have privacy practices separate from those of OpionZilla. It is recommended you review the privacy policies of any third party site you may be directed to from our email messages.

3rd Party Service Providers: There are several reasons your personal information may be provided to our third party service providers and they are as follows: provide you with our or partner companies product offers, deploying email, postal, and online campaigns; data processing, data warehousing, data verification and supplementation; market research, fulfillment, and technical support. You consent to this transfer, storing and processing of data, when providing your information. Personal information held by HomeProjectPros.org, its affiliates, agents and/or service providers may be located in a variety of countries as necessary to provide the services contemplated herein.

All third party service providers are bound by contract to protect members personal information and abide by commitments made in this Privacy Policy, subject to the laws of the jurisdiction in which the information is held. This may include lawful requirements to disclose personal information to government authorities.

Legal Requests: We may also disclose your personal information, as required by law, such as in response to a subpoena, a lawful request by public authority, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or similar legal process, and when we believe necessary in connection with an investigation of fraud, property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Merger or Consolidation: We may share personal information and other data in the events such as merger, consolidation, financing, securitization, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of HomeProjectPros.org or our business or assets. This would take place for the purpose of performing the proposed or actual transaction provided that such a third party consents to honor made in this Privacy Policy.

Summary Reports and Analysis: Anonymous research reports are compiled with your survey responses, email activity, or online activity combined with information from other consumers. These reports will not personally identify you. The reports are used to help improve our and our partners offers, products and services to better serve you. These reports may be provided to third parties for analysis or other purposes.

### Cookies And Online Activity

HomeProjectPros.org and its partners or third party providers use the standard cookie feature of major browser applications, web beacons and similar items on our website for multiple reasons. Information is collected when you visit our site, including how you use our website, device information, browser and operating system and other information to help us determine products and services appropriate for our consumers.

Modifying Your browser settings: At any point you can modify your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie. You will have the choice of whether or not to accept it. In the event you reject cookies, you may still use HomeProjectPros.org but some areas may be limited. Below are resources to information on managing your cookie settings within common browsers.

### Choices And Managing Your Membership

As a member of HomeProjectPros.org you have the choice to decide which programs you wish to participate in and offers you receive.

Email offers: To discontinue receiving email offers at any time, follow the “Unsubscribe” instructions on any email sent to you by HomeProjectPros.org or by writing to us via email at unsubscribe@helpfulfunds.org or via post mail address as indicated in “Contact Us” below.

Product offers: To discontinue receiving product offers from our partner companies, please contact those companies directly. HomeProjectPros.org is not responsible for for the behavior of third party partner companies that you are referred to from HomeProjectPros.org.

### Security

HomeProjectPros.org is commitment to providing data security and strive to make certain that our partners incorporate the latest encryption and security devices to prevent loss, misuse or alteration.

### Terms and Conditions

HomeProjectPros.org products and services are intended for residents of the United States that are over 18 years of age.

By becoming a registered member of HomeProjectPros.org, providing your contact information and answers to surveys, and/or using any of the services provided by HomeProjectPros.org, you consent to abiding by our Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy. We recommend you view our Terms and Conditions.

### Policy Modifications

This privacy policy may be updated to reflect changes to our information practices. In the event any changes are made, a notice will be posted on this page along with the updated Privacy Policy prior to the change becoming effective. We recommend you periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. You can determine when this policy was last revised by checking the “last updated” legend at the top of this policy.

### Contact Us

For questions regarding HomeProjectPros.org or this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

By Mail: 1312 17th Street #548, Denver, CO 80202 USA

By Email: contact@homeprojectpros.org
